NICOLAS TOPORCOV

ntoporcov@me.com (904) 704 3653

Education

University of North Florida

B.S. in Communication Class of 2015

Skills

Basic Level

AdWords Sketch Analytics React

InVision React Native

Intermediate Level

Git UX Design PHP Prototyping

Advanced Level

HTML Illustrator
CSS Adobe XD
JQuery UI Design
Javascript Print Design
Photoshop Ad Design
InDesign Wordpress

.. and I also enjoy:

Photography Animating Videography Reddit-ing

Experience

GleanView July 2017 - Now

Marketing Front-End Developer and Product Designer

GleanView is where I started learning about web development and product design from scratch. I've been responsible for the entire website and landing pages design and development, all google display ads design, company blog design and setup in wordpress and more recently product design for the software itself.

Lunic Visuals

January 2017 - Now

Co-Owner

Lunic is a company I started with my wife to offer Photography and Videography. We've been doing mostly engagement photoshoots and wedding photography and videography. I also designed and developed our website in wordpress.

Jacksonville Business Journal

February 2016 - June 2017

Graphic Designer

The Jacksonville Business Journal was my first full-time employment where I was responsible for design. I was responsible for designing, placing and managing ads being sold for the weekly newspaper as well as the annual Book of Lists. While working at the JBJ I learned a lot about Design in itself, specially how to deal with deadlines and handling super short notices.

JAX Chamber	UNF COAS	UNF Int'l Center
Design Intern	Student Instructor	Student Assistant
2015 Summer	2015 Fall and Spring	2014 - 2015

Introduction

You probably noticed already, but my name is Nicolas Toporcov. I am a former communication student from UNF turned Graphic Designer turned Web Designer, Front-End Developer and UI/UX Designer.

I wasn't born working though, in fact, I was born in São Paulo, Brazil in 1992. Around 20 years later I started working for this company that assisted Brazilian students to go to college here in the states. One college I was always in contact with was UNF, and once while talking to one of the admission officers for international students of UNF, she told me I could come study here on a scholarship. So I did.

At UNF I met my wife, Luiza, who also happened to be Brazilian. Together, we also started Lunic Visuals, which has been steadfastly growing in the photography and videography wedding business.